I see the mask come down again A stranger where my
friend has been I feel the static start to rise
Behind the emptiness in your eyes You're
building walls of steel and stone And I'm so
scared you're all alone I'm reaching out, but
silently Oh brother please, come back to me This
is the unspoken word, the space between the
lines A desperate signal, a secret sign More
than a feeling, more than a touch It's knowing
that I miss you much You're not alone, I'm not
alone On this dark path you've been thrown
He's standing there, a ghost in white
Stealing all your precious light I see the
future, dark and grey As he prepares to take you
away I'm playing our song, a desperate prayer To
let you know that I am still there The only way
that I know how To save you from this broken vow
This is the unspoken word The space between the
lines A desperate signal, a secret sign
More than a touch, it's knowing that I miss you
much You're not alone, I'm not alone On this dark
path you've been thrown